Guide to the National Campus Ministry Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- N.C.M.A. Filing System, 1964-1987; Series I
  - 1973-1974
    - Task Force on Restructuring: Correspondence and Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Task Force on Restructuring: Questionnaire Responses, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Council for Professional Religious Leadership in Higher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Faculty Forum Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Conferences: Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Conferences: Southeast Campus Ministers' Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Conferences: Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - National Council of Churches, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Project Forward '76, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - 1974-1975
    - General Matters, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Budget and Finance, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Budget and Finance (cont'd), 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Checks and Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Elections Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 94)
    - Regional Representatives, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Campus Christian Ministry, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Coordinating Council of Professional Religious, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Assns. in Higher Education (C.C.P.R.A.H.E.), 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - National Institute for Campus Ministries, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - United Christian Ministry, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - United Methodist Church, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - United Ministries in Higher Education, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - United States Catholic Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Women in Campus Ministry, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Conferences, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - NACUC/ACURA, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
  - 1975-1976
    - General Matters, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - General Matters, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - Elections Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Budget and Finance, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 102)
    - Checks and Bills, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Checks and Bills (cont'd), 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 103)
    - Membership Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - Membership Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 105)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Misc. Papers (incl. notes on "Findings" Proceedings Book), 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Regional Representatives, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 108)
    - Campus Ministry Advancement, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 109)
    - Campus Ministry Women, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 110)
    - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - NICM, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - UMHE, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - United Methodist Church (incl. Board of Higher Education and Ministry, U.M.C.), 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 111)
    - United Methodists in Campus Ministry -Convocation material, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 112)
    - Conferences Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 113)
  - 1976-1977
    - General Matters, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 114)
    - Budget and Finance, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 115)
    - Checks and Bills, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 116)
    - Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 117)
    - Regional Representatives, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - Membership, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - C.C.M.A., 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 119)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - International Nestle Boycott Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - N.I.C.M., 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - United Methodist Church, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 120)
    - U.M.H.E., 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - Conferences - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
  - 1977-1978
    - General Matters, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 121)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
    - Budget and Finance, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 122)
    - Checks and Bills, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 123)
    - Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 124)
    - Regional Representatives, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 125)
    - Membership, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 126)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 127)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 128)
    - North American Youth Coalition for Global Interdependence, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
    - Third Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
    - United Methodist Church, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - 1978-1979
    - General Matters, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 129)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - Budget and Finance, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 130)
    - Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 131)
    - Regional Representatives, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - Membership, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 132)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 133)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 134)
    - Campus Ministry Advancement, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 135)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - I.T.E.S.T., 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - International Dimensions of Youth and Young Adult Ministries, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education (M.B.H.E.), 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - National Institute for Campus Ministries, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - Third Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 135A)
    - United Methodist Church, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - United Campus Ministry, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - United Ministries in Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - University Lutheran Chapel, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - World Council of Churches (Unit III Working Group), 1978-1979 (Box 24)
  - 1979-1980
    - General Matters, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 136)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - Budget and Finance, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 137)
    - Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 138)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 139)
    - Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 140)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 141)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 142)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - United Campus Ministry, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - Young Christians for Global Justice: An Ecumenical Council in North America, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - Conferences: European Student Chaplains' Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - Conferences: NCMA Conference (4th Ecumenical, Denver), 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - 1980-1981
    - General Matters, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 143)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
    - Executive Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 144)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 145)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 146)
    - INFACT, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 147)
    - United Campus Ministry, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
    - United Methodist Church, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
    - United Ministries in Education, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
  - 1981-1982
    - General Matters, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 148)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 25)
    - Budget and Finance, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 149)
    - Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 150)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 151)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 152)
    - Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 153)
    - NCMA Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 154)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 155)
    - U.M.C., 1981-1982 (Box 25)
    - U.M.E., 1981-1982 (Box 25)
  - 1982-1983
    - General Matters, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 156)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
    - Elections Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 157)
    - Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 158)
    - Membership, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 159)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 160)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - 1983-1984
    - General Matters, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 162)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 26)
    - Budget and Finance, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 163)
    - Executive Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 164)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 165)
    - Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 166)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 167)
    - Elections Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 168)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 169)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 26)
    - U.M.C., 1983-1984 (Box 26)
  - 1984-1985
    - General Matters, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 170)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1984-1985 (Box 26)
    - Budget and Finance, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 171)
    - Elections Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 172)
    - Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 173)
    - Membership, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 174)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 175)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 176)
    - NCMA Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 177)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 178)
    - U.M.C., 1984-1985 (Box 26)
    - U.M.E., 1984-1985 (Box 26)
  - 1985-1986
    - General Matters, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 179)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 26)
    - Budget and Finance, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 180)
    - Elections Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 181)
    - Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 182)
    - Membership, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 183)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 184)
    - U.M.C., 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 185)
    - Unitas, 1985-1986 (Box 27)
    - Conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 186)
  - 1986-1987
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 187)
  - Undated material
    - General Matters, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 188)
    - Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Memos, n.d. (Box 27)
    - NCMA Statements and Brochures (Box 27)
    - Elections Committee, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 189)
    - Executive Committee, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 190)
    - Membership, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 191)
    - American Baptist, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 192)
    - C.C.P.R.A.H.E., n.d. (Box 27)
    - Church Society for College Work, n.d. (Box 27)
    - Coalition for the Right to Eat, n.d. (Box 27)
    - Council for Prof. Leadership in H. E., n.d. (Box 27)
    - Lilly Foundation (Box 27)
    - M.B.H.E./N.C.M.A./U.M.C., n.d. (Box 27)
    - National Ecumenical Student Council, n.d. (Box 27)
    - National Institute for Campus Ministries, n.d. (Box 27)
    - U.M.E., n.d. (Box 27)
    - U.M.H.E., n.d. (Box 27)
    - NCMA Newsletter, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 193)
    - Checks and Bills (Box 27, Folder 194)
    - Conferences, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 195)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 196)
- 1997 Addendum, 1992-1997; Series II
  - Coordinating Committee minutes, 1992-1997 (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - Occasional Papers, 1991-1997 (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - Newsletters, 1986-1991 (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - Newsletters, 1992-1997 (Box 28, Folder 200)
  - History of the NCMA, 1964-1994: A Brief History by Charles Doak; A Briefer History by George Gunn (Box 28, Folder 201)
- 2010 Addendum, 1971-2006; Series III
  - Articles of Incorporation, Constitution, By-Laws, 1975-1997 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - List of Executive Committee members, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1998-2005 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Coordinating Committee minutes, 1998-2006 (Box 29, Folder 4-6)
  - Partnership Program, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Membership lists, 1997-2005 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence / files of NCMA President Ken McIntosh, 1996-1998 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence / files of George W. and Sally Gunn, including re. NCMA publications, 1991-1997 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Realm of Higher Education - NCMA Newsletter, 1996-2006 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - Occasional Papers, 1990-2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - NCMA summer conference brochures, 1994,1998-2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Membership brochures, 1971, 1990s-2006 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Re. professional standards, code of ethics - Catholic Campus Ministry Association, United Methodists in Campus Ministry, Presbyterian Ministers in Higher Education, 1996, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Re. bulk rating mailings, 1994-1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Collection of logos, letterhead/envelope addresses for campus ministry organizations, 1980s, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- 2013 Addendum, Series IV
  Documentation provided by John S. Duley who was a campus minister from 1948 thru 1968. At Michigan State University Duley was a founder at of the Student Tutorial Education Project (STEP) with Rust College in Mississippi. This program operating 1965-1968 was provided an opportunity for activist students to do service outside of Michigan particularly in the area of civil rights.
  - Interviews about the "STEP" Program between Michigan State University and Rust College, Mississippi (2 DVDs), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Writings by John S. Duley: "Laity Papers: A Phoenix-Like Life Experience", no date (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Writings by John S. Duley: "Notes from the Margins: An Ode to the Holy Spirit", 2007 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Writings and biographical information about John S. Duley, 1982-2012 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- 2015 Addendum
  - Writings by John S. Duley: "Service Learning and Civic Engagement as Preparation for a Life Committed to Working for the Common Good: The Michigan State University/Rust College Student Tutorial Education Project, 1965-1968 (co-written with Nicole C. Springer, in Going Public: Civic and Community Engagement" (Michigan State University Press, 2013) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Writings by John S. Duley: "The Work of the Church in the University: Four Obstacles" in The Christian Scholar; "The Ever Present Possibility", 1959, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 50th anniversary publication: Campus Ministry Memoirs: The Way It Was 1964-2014, edited by Betsy Alden (Box 32, Folder 3)